Inventory of the Cabell Family Papers 1693-1913, 1743-1823
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- Manuscripts 1736-1878, n.d., MsV.
  - Miscellaneous entries in diary, 1878., MsV. 31. (Box 12)
  - Legal accounts, 1804-1824., MsV. 32. (Box 12)
  - Notes by Alexander Brown, n.d., MsV. 33. (Box 12)
  - Postage and newspaper accounts, n.d., MsV. 34. (Box 12)